扩音器:本西沃,准备进来!
Loudspeaker: Ben Seaver get your hollow head in here!
德威特:西-沃-先-生?你以为我是个傻瓜吗?
Mr.Dewitt: M-i-s-t-e-r Seaver?Do you think that I'm a fool?
本:先生,我只是重复别人说过的话.
Ben: Sir, I was just repeating what everyone else was saying.
德威特:哦,别耍贫嘴.
Mr.Dewitt: Oh, don't smart-mouth me.
你竟然申请参加高级再编班考试.
You have requested an application for the advanced placement exam.
你到底想干什么?举行冒牌消防演习?
What are you planning to do?Stage a fake fire drill?Fire a smoke bomb?
乱放烟雾弹?找个漂亮妞?
Hire a stripper?
本:先生,如果我有钱找个漂亮妞的话,我愿意
Ben: Sir, if I could afford a stripper, I like...
本:我没什么打算.我申请,只是因为我真想考一下.
Ben: I am not playing anything.I signed from the test because I really wanna
take it
德威特:别发誓了.你想让我相信本西沃已经是大学生了吗?
Mr.Dewitt: Hold you promise.You expect me to believe that you, Ben Seaver, are
college bound
本:是的!我是.这就是我参加考试的原因.
Ben: Yes!I am, that's why I wanna take the test.
德威特:可西沃先生,
Mr.Dewitt: But Mr.Seaver, you're a pathetic student.
你是一个差等生.
And the only person with worse grades than you is that kid who got hit
同学里只有那个被闪电击中过的孩子成绩比你差.
by lightning.
本:是的,我比斯巴基好多了!?
Ben: Sure I am doing much better than Sparky!?
本:求了你,查查我的成绩单!
Ben: Please, check my grades!
德威特:全是优良?
Mr.Dewitt: A three point O (3.0)?
德威特:德克斯特小姐,别添乱了.
Mr.Dewitt: Ms.Dexter, put down that bottle.
有人破译了计算机安全密码.
Someone has cracked the computer security code.
本:我是用这些课本破译的.如果不相信,
Ben: All I've been cracking are these books, if you don't believe me,
你可以问我的老师去.
please ask my teachers.
德威特:明白了.
Mr.Dewitt: Lachaim!
德威特:哦,好吧,西沃先生,我可以同意你的考试申请.不过,如果我发现你在成绩单上动了手脚…
Mr.Dewitt: Well, yeah, Mr.Seaver, I am going to give you the application for
the exam... But if I find out that you've been tampering with your grades
本:先生,我没动任何手脚!
Ben: Sir, I haven't tampered with anything!
我发誓本四沃是个优等生.相信我!
I swear that I Ben Seaver am a 3.0 student.Believe me!
开萝尔:布赖恩!你干什么?
Carol: Brianne!What are you doing?
布赖恩:开萝尔,我厌倦这种生活了.
Brianne: Carol, I'm tired of being selfish,
我做出了一个将要改变我们俩生活的决定.
I have made a decision that will change both of our lives!
开萝尔:你想跟被你甩掉的人重归于好吗?
Carol: You're gonna pick up your toe nails after you clipped them?
布赖恩:不!这一次,
Brianne: No!I finally realize this time I give a little back.
我终于认识到可以做点有意义的事了.我在非洲找了份工作.
So I am talking a job in Africa.
开萝尔:你要去第三世界工作吗?
Carol: You are going to work in a third world country?
布赖恩:我不知道到底是第几世界的国家.
Brianne: I'm not sure what number it is.
好吧,你要在医院工作吗?盖房子?种地?
Carol: Well, will you be working in hospitals?Building homes?Farming?
布赖恩:比这强.
Brianne: Better: I'll be teaching low-impact aerobics at a Club made in
我要在塞内加尔的一家俱乐部里教健身操.
Senegal!
开萝尔:布赖恩,让我说什么好呢?
Carol: Brianne, I don't know what to say?
布赖恩:哦,你会想念我的!
Brianne: Oh, you're gonna miss me!
开萝尔:满不是这么回事!
Carol: That hardly describes it!
布赖恩:我得去赶飞机去了!
Brianne: I got a plane to catch!
开萝尔:布赖恩,我不会忘记你的!
Carol: Brianne, I will never forget you!
布赖恩:不要太悲伤.哦,我很坚强.
Brianne: Don't you cry.Oh I'll be strong.
开萝尔:终于结束了!她走了!
Carol: It's over!She's gone!
女士们,先生们,布赖恩终于滚-蛋-了.
L-ladies and gentlemen, Brianne has l-e-f-t the building.
卢克:嘿,干什么呢?
Luke: Hey what's shaking?
本:我在跟克莉丝玩捉迷藏呢.
Ben: I am playing a game of hide-n-eat with Chrissy.
卢克:在玩捉迷藏吗?
Luke: Isn't it hide and seek?
本:是的,我们各有各的玩法.
Ben: Well, you play your way I'll play mine.
卢克:高级再编班考试.哇,聪明的小子!
Luke: The advanced placement exam.Whooo smart guy!
本:小声点,我不想让妈妈和爸爸知道.
Ben: Keep it down, I don't want mom and dad to know.
如果我不及格,没人会笑话我的.
If I fail, nobody will be the wiser.
迈克:嘿,兄弟们,
Mike: Hey guys, where is dad?
爸爸呢?在他见到会计之前,我得跟他借点钱.
I need to hit him up for a loan before he meets with his account.
杰森:你以为我是印钞机?
Jason: Do you think I am made of money?
噢,太晚了…
Mike: Phew.Too late...
开萝尔:你们肯定猜不到发生什么了?布赖恩搬出宿舍了.
Carol: You guys will never guess what happened.
这学期就是我一个人住了.
Brianne moved out and I am gonna be alone for the rest of this semester.
迈克:开萝尔,醒醒吧,这一辈子你都得一个人过了.
Mike: Carol wake up, you're gonna be alone for the rest of your life.
开萝尔:你们想笑就笑吧,我是来收拾东西的,
Carol: You guys can laugh if you want but I am here to pack up and
我要永远地离开这里了.从此以后你们再也看不到我了.
leave this place forever.You've seen this face for the last time.
卢克:有谁想再见她吗?
Luke: Does anyone wanna feel that one?
迈克:哦,你们太麻木了!还要我提醒开萝尔对我们是非常重要的吗?
Mike: Great, we will play numb!May I remind you that Carol is very important to us?
卢克:呃,你说的对.她是你妹妹.
Luke: Er, You're right, she is your sister.
迈克:她走了,你就可以占有她的房间了.
Mike: Well, to heck with that, she's got a room that you could have.
开萝尔:完全正确,是你的了!开萝尔不再住这里了.
Carol: Absolutely, it's yours!Carol does not live here anymore.
迈克:太好了.嘿,
Mike: Great.Hey you better get the car,
你最好要辆车,我们可以把你的东西扔出窗外.
we'll just throw your jacket out the window.
卢克:太好了,一从图书馆回来,
Luke: This is great,
我就搬进去.
as soon as I get back from the library I am moving in.
克莉丝:我就知道你找不到我.
Chrissy: I think you never find me.
本:就是啊.
Ben: I think so, too.
克莉丝:好了,本,该你藏了.
Chrissy: Ok, Ben.Now turn to you hide.
本:噢,真的?噢,衣服!
Ben: Oooh, really?Oooh, coats!
克莉丝:10,20,30,30,
Chrissy: Ten, twenty, thirty, thirty, thirty, hundred!
30,100!我才不上你的当呢.
Aw, I am not falling for that.
会计师:我是一个专业会计师,
CPA: I realize I am a licensed CPA,
不过,我还是用浅显的语言向你解释:如果你不递交帐单,
but I'll try to explain it in layman's terms:
就拿不到钱!
If you don't send bills you don't get paid!
杰森:哦,开萝尔曾经把我的数据输入到电脑里了.
Jason: Well, Carol used to input my data on computer,
可她现在在学校呢.
now she's away at college.
会计师:别的孩子不能帮你吗?
CPA: Can't one of your other kids help?
杰森:噢,对了.迈克太忙了,克莉丝才5岁,
Jason: Ugh yeah, Mike's too busy, Chrissy's five, and Ben,
本是个好孩子,不过算了吧,他可没有数学脑子.
he's a sweet kid but let's face it, he's no Einstein.
杰森:哦,你换了辆新车吗?
Jason: Oh, you're driving a Lamborghini?
会计师:快去开你的帐单吧.
CPA: I am not behind in my billings.
杰森:我能试试吗?
Jason: Can I honk the horn?
克莉丝:哦,他不会藏这的.
Chrissy: Alright he wouldn't.He might?!This is where I hid!
他会吗?这是我藏过的地方!你怎么这么笨呢?
How stupid can you be?
本:问爸爸去.
Ben: Ask dad.
迈克:哈罗,打搅了,你有什么事吗?
Mike: Hello, excuse me.Can I help you?
德怀特:我在欣赏你家屋顶呢.听说,这段时间来这里的人都排成队了.
Dwight: I was just admiring the pitch of your roof.It's been said, people have
been stating up there all this time
迈克:呃,信不信由你,你是第一个.呵呵,呃,你是修屋顶的吗?
Mike: Uhm, believe it or not, you're the first!Hehe, uh, are you a uh roofer?
德怀特:哦,不!这只是我的爱好.
Dwight: Oh no!It's only a hobby.
迈克:这样啊.
Mike: I see.
德怀特:我是你家的新邻居!你知道"新维多利亚屋"吗?
Dwight: I am your new neighbour!Do you know the neo-Victorian House?
迈克:什么
Mike: The what?
德怀特:具有文艺复兴风格的建筑!
Dwight: With the renaissance influence!
迈克:你在说什么呢?
Mike: What're you talking about?
德怀特:就这条街,离这不远…
Dwight: This tree, three houses down...
迈克:!哦!哦,呃,
Mike: Oh!Oh, uh, I um, a little advice, if you ever order pizza,
我,呃,提个小建议.要是你订比萨,把你的地址告诉我.
just give'em your address.
德怀特:哈哈哈.
Dwight: hahaha.
迈克:呵呵呵,让我猜猜,你是开萝尔的朋友,是吧?
Mike: Hehehe, let me take a wild shot, you're a friend of Carol's right?
德怀特:开萝尔?开萝尔?呃,哈,哈--哈,我对这个名字念念不忘.
Dwight: Carol?Carol?Uh-haah , ooooooooh, I can say that name for hours.
迈克:哦,别这样.呃.我刚吃完饭.好吗?
Mike: Well, please don't, uh, I just ate.Ok?
迈克:嘿,下来,开萝尔!
Mike: Hey, Go down, the librarian!
开萝尔:德怀特?
Carol: Dwight?
德怀特:噢,噢,你还是我见过的最漂亮的女孩.
Dwight: Ru-hoo.You're still the prettiest girl I've ever seen.
开萝尔:德怀特,你从哪里来?
Carol: Dwight, where did you come from?
德怀特:这条街, 就这附近…
Dwight: This tree, three houses down...
开萝尔:那个具有文艺复兴风格的"新新维多利亚屋"吗?
Carol: The neo-Victorian House with the renaissance influence?
德怀特:是的!我一个月前租下了它.这样在我攻读中世纪研究博士学位的时候可以靠近你.
Dwight: Yes!I rented a month ago to be near you while I work on my PhD in medieval studies.
开萝尔:不过,从那次舞会后,我们就没有说过一句话啊.
Carol: But we have not even spoken since the dance of the Catskills.
德怀特:你忘了吗,我告诉过你我要搬到长岛来,这样我们就可以在一起了.
Dwight: Don't you remember that I told you then that I'd be moving to Long Island so that we could be together
开萝尔:你说的是"再见"啊.
Carol: You said, "See you around!"
德怀特:是的,然后第二天我就搬来了.
Dwight: Right, and then the next day I moved here.
开萝尔:一个月前为了靠近我你就搬来了.
Carol: You moved here a month ago to be near me,
可这是你第一次来找我吗?
and this is the first time that you've come over?
德怀特:我不想表现地太急躁.
Dwight: I didn't wanna appear to forward.
开萝尔:哇,你知道,
Carol: Wow.You know, nobody has ever changed their zip code for me.
还没人为了我而搬家呢.也许有人会为了而走出家门.我不知道说什么才好.
They probably went out the door for me.I don't know what to say!
德怀特:知道了.我给你施加压力了.推你,推你,推你!那我下个月再来吧!
Dwight: I knew it.I am arsing you.Pushee pushee pushee!I'll come back next month!
开萝尔:不,等等.这种感觉太甜蜜了!我很高兴你把家搬过来.
Carol: No, wait, I think it's sweet!And I'm glad you tracked me down.
德怀特:太好了,呵呵.
Dwight: Groovy, hehe.
德怀特:你愿意到我家坐一坐,听几首宗教赞歌吗?
Dwight: Would you like to come to my house and listen to some Gagarian Chants?
开萝尔:你有它们的唱片吗
Carol: You have them on CD?
德怀特:不,是我唱.
Dwight: No, I sign them.
开萝尔:太棒了.
Carol: Groovy.
肯:嘿,本,怎么了?
Ken: Hey, yo, Ben, What's up?
本:没什么.
Ben: Nothing.
肯:看起来,你跟丑八怪就像孪生兄弟似的.你看,我弄到了一本,并不比我们想像地那么难.听这段:
Ken: You look like you fell outta your twin bubble-a-zaggin. Did you know
I got this study guide for advance placement exam and it's not as hard as
we thought, listen to this
肯:三个男孩喝一罐三加仑的水.假如第一个男孩比其他两个男孩多喝一倍.那每人各喝多少?
Ken: Three boys share three quart canteen of oar.If the first boy drinks twice
as much as the other two what do they each gain
本:把嘴都灌满了.
Ben: A mouth full of backwash.
肯:你怎么了?昨天你还热衷于谈论考试呢.
Ken: What's with you?Yesterday you were all pumped up about taking the test.
本:是的,那是在我玩捉迷藏之前的事了.
Ben: Yeah, well, that was before I played hide-n-seek.
卢克:就这样,
Luke: Okay, first time we'll move all the killed-stuff animals to the attic,
我打算先把所有的那些该死的动物标本扔到阁楼上.我还要扔掉那些烂花,
I am gonna get rid of all those dead flowers,
不过我们得留一张狗玩扑克的图片.
and then we are gonna get one of those pictures of dogs playing poker.
迈克:噢,噢,噢,别都扔了,我还得给凯特搞一个生日礼物呢.
Mike: Oooh, oooh, oooh, don't get too light, I need a birthday present for Kate.
布兰科杜德:这是我进入名牌大学的通行证.
Black Dude: This is my ticket to a good university,
我不想在阿尔夫兰登这样的末流大学混到最后.
I don't wanna end up Alf Landen Junior College.
他们的入学考试猜放在罐子里的豆子的数量.
You know their entrance exam is guessing the number of beans in a jar!
卢克:呃,迈克,别在阿尔夫兰登学了.
Luke: Um, Mike, quit the Alf Landen.
迈克:实话告诉你,数豆子的把戏可不是那么容易.
Mike: For your information, that bean thing isn't half as easy as it sounds!
本:踢他-伊特!
Ben: Teet-eet!
杰森:嘿,孩子们,谁来帮我弄柴火.
Jason: Hey guys, I could use some assistance for firewood.
迈克:对不起,我不行.我和卢克要整理开萝尔的房间.
Mike: Sorry no can do, Luke and I got a few minutes to get Carol's room.
杰森:哦,本,你能去捡4,5根干木柴来吗?
Jason: Oh Ben, could pick four or five good dry logs please?
杰森:肯,你不进来喝杯热巧克力?
Jason: Ken, you wanna come in for some hot chocolate?
肯:哦,不了,谢谢你西沃医生.我要回家做功课了.
Ken: Oh no thank you Dr.Seaver I gotta go home, and study.
杰森:噢,书房(跟功课是一个单词).
Jason: Awww, study, but to my boys study is just a room where Mrs.
对我的孩子来说,书房就是孔雀夫人用铅管杀死芥末姑娘的地方.
Peacock killed girl Mustard with a lead pipe.
肯:哦,明天我们在一起复习这个吗?
Ken: Well, you wanna get together and review this tomorrow?
本:再说吧.
Ben: We'll see.
开萝尔:(吃吃地笑)我真不敢相信我们在一起已经过了6个小时!
Carol: (chuckles) We can't believe we just spent the last six hours together!
德怀特:我知道,过的真快,好像只有2小时38分钟似的.
Dwight: I know I know it only seemed like two hours and thirty eight minutes!
开萝尔:真惊讶我们有这么多的共同语言.
Carol: It's amazing how much we have in common.
我真不相信有人竟然知道与历届总统的生日相搭配的宝石.
I can't believe somebody actually knows all the presidents' birth stones.
德怀特:给你说实话吧,
Dwight: I have to be honest with you;
米勒德菲尔莫尔的宝石是我碰巧猜对的.
Millard Fillmore's Turquoise was just a lucky guess.
德怀特:开萝尔,以前我从没有这样的感觉,
Dwight: Carol, I've never felt such an intense connection with anyone
与一个人竟然这么恋恋不舍.我心里像着火一样.
else before.I am on fire.
开萝尔:我也是.我身上有一种触电的感觉.
Carol: Me too.I can feel the electricity flowing through my body.
我再也等不下去了.(接吻)
I can't wait another minute.(smooch)
德怀特:真激动.
Dwight: Oh-hoo.
开萝尔:我也是.
Carol: Me too.
德怀特:从今往后,这就是我们约会的地方.
Dwight: From now on, this will be our drive-way.
明天我们还能在在见面吗?
Can we meet right here tomorrow?
开萝尔:哦,不!我刚刚收拾了东西要离开家.
Carol: Oh no! I just packed up all my stuff for them to give-away,
我告诉家里我永远不再见他们了.明-天,就这样.
I am telling my family they'd never see me again. To-mo-rrow it is.
麦琪:开萝尔,我以为你回学校了!
Maggie: Carol, I thought you'd gone to New York!
开萝尔:妈妈,最神奇的事情发生了.
Carol: Mother, the most amazing thing has happened.
你还记得那次舞会上的德怀特霍利伯顿吗?
Do you remember Dwight Halliburton from the Catskills?
麦琪:那个总爱敲自己脑袋的人?
Maggie: The one who kept hitting himself in the head?
开萝尔:是的.你猜怎么着:现在他成了我们的邻居了.
Carol: Right, and guess what: Now he's doing it in our neighbourhood.
他抛弃了一切搬到我的身边了.
He has uprooted his whole life to move near me.
麦琪:哦,这听起来真浪漫.很古怪,但很浪漫.
Maggie: Well that sounds very romantic.Bizarre, but romantic.
开萝尔:所以,我今晚要住在这里.
Carol: So, I have to stay here tonignt
麦琪:我听说你把房间给卢克了,今天.
Maggie: I heard you gave your room to Luke today.
开萝尔:哦,这没什么.我,
Carol: Oh, well that's ok, I ,uh, I'll sleep on a foldable, sleep on a roof,
呃,我可以睡在折叠床上,睡在屋顶上,
If I can get any sleep at all.
有个地方睡就行.我像小鸟一样飞翔,像风儿一样起舞.
I am soaring like a bird, dancing like a breeze.
麦琪:像鸭子一样喋喋不休.
Maggie: Chattering like a baboon.
开萝尔:哦,迈克,你真逗!
Carol: Oh Mike, you are so funny!
杰森:哦,不,不,
Jason: Oh, no no no Ben not like that.
本,这样的不行.我告诉你要拿干的木柴,
I thought I told you to get dry ones Ben?
是不是?请回去再拿些干的.动动脑子.
Go get a couple more please, use your head.
麦琪:嘿,本,过来尝尝热巧克力.
Maggie: Hey Ben, just the guy to test-taste the hot chocolate.
本:我不渴.
Ben: I am not thirsty.
克莉丝:我喝一杯.他不配喝这种好喝的东西.
Chrissy: I'll take his.He should not have all that sugar anyway.
麦琪:杰森,本出什么事了?
Maggie: Jason, what's wrong with Ben?
杰森:麦琪,你的问题太宽泛了.
Jason: Maggie that's such a broad question.
麦琪:不,今天晚上,
Maggie: No, tonight, first he did not touch his dinner,
他先是不吃晚饭,接着又不喝热巧克力.这不是本的作风.
then he passes up hot chocolate!For Ben that's quiet.
杰森:他很好.
Jason: He's fine, I saw him on the ground goofing up with Kenny just a
几分钟前我还我看见他跟肯在闲聊呢.
couple of minutes ago.
杰森:啊,太好了.是的,干木柴!
Jason: Aw, perfect, yes, dry ones!Now, they'll go like that.
现在,就要这么做.对了,看,火着了.
Right, that, that's a fire.
开萝尔:嘿,我忍不住要称赞你的屋顶.
Carol: Hi, I could not help by admire the pitch of your roof.
愿意吃点松饼吗?
Care to nibble on my muffins?
金发女郎:你找谁?
Blondie: Can I help you?
开萝尔:德怀特在吗?
Carol: Is D-wight here?
金发女郎:哦,他在洗澡呢.我转告他,好吗?
Blondie: Oh, he, he's in the shower.Can I take a message?
开萝尔:哦,屋顶,搬家,吃松饼.我希望你俩都噎死!
Carol: Well, roof, pitch, nibble, Well I hope you both chew!
杰森:哦,哇,哇,怎么了这里?
Jason: Oh ho ho, what happened here?
麦琪:开萝尔给她的新男朋友做了松饼.
Maggie: Carol made muffins for her new boyfriend.
杰森:啊,开萝尔有了新男朋友,哦,松饼?谁是开萝尔的这个新男朋友?
Jason: Ah, Carol's got a new boyfriend, Boo, muffins?So who's this new boyfriend of Carol's?
麦琪:你还记得德怀特,那个在上次的舞会上跟我跳狐步舞的小伙子吗?
Maggie: Well you remember Dwight, the one I fox-trotted with at Catskill's?
杰森:哦,哈哈,那个经常敲自己脑袋的人.
Jason: Oh, haha the one who hits himself a lot.
麦琪:哦,我预感这次可能是真的.
Maggie: Uhm, I got a hunch this could be the one.
我还从没见过开萝尔这样对待一个小伙子呢.
I've never seen Carol act this way over a boy before?
杰森:嘿,早上好,
Jason: Hey, Morning sweetheart?
亲爱的.哦,你还没告诉我你有了新男朋友呢?
Oh you didn't tell me about this new boyfriend?
开萝尔:男朋友?我没男朋友.
Carol: Boyfriend?I have no boyfriend.
杰森:不是德怀特吗?
Jason: I thought Dwight?
开萝尔:德怀特?
Carol: Dwight?Please!Just give me a little credit,
拜托!给我点自尊吧.
since when does Carol Seaver have to lower her standards for a fork-tongued
您什么时候见过开萝尔西沃这么屈尊跟一个中世纪的大舌头臭虫交往呢.
medieval maggot!
杰森:对不起,我不是故意的.
Jason: Sorry my mistake.
开萝尔:重申一下:从现在开始,开萝尔西沃再也不在这里生活了.
Carol: And another thing: As of this moment,
从此我就是纽约人了.
Carol Seaver does not live here anymore.Ich bin ein New Yorker!
杰森:噢!
Jason: Jawohl!
本:开萝尔,能问你件事吗?
Ben: Carol, can I ask you something?
开萝尔:本,现在不是时候.
Carol: Ben, this is not a good time.
本:你觉得我笨吗?
Ben: Do you think I'm dumb?
开萝尔:是的.!
Carol: Yes!
本:哦,这是个严肃的问题.你觉得我蠢吗?
Ben: Well, it's a serious question.Do you think I am stupid?
开萝尔:本,你比嚼过的口香糖还笨,
Carol: Ben, you're dumber than used chewing gum, you have the IQ of a saw,
你的智商连木头都不如.
doesn't even your dryer set to fluff,
如果觉得还不够,我一定再恭维你几句.
you need anymore I'll have to get back to you.
德威特先生:西沃先生!
Mr.Dewitt: Mister Seaver!
迈克:嗨!
Mike: Heh!
德威特先生:很久不见了.
Mr.Dewitt: Long time no see.
德威特先生:我无事不登三宝殿.
Mr.Dewitt: I guess my rash was stress-related.
迈克:哦,很高兴见到您.你怎么穿着燕尾服像跟香蕉似的.
Mike: Well, it's nice to see you too. Why, you're dressed like Tuxedo Banana.
德威特先生:西沃先生,
Mr.Dewitt: Mr.Seaver,
你以前在我手下的时候,因为教育法我不便对你施加拳脚;现在你毕业了,
when you were under my tutelage I was prohibited by law from inflecting
我可以好好地教训教训你了.
bodily harm; Now that you've matriculated, I can wail the totter outta ya.
迈克:嘿,爸爸,有人找你!
Mike: Hey, dad, it's for you!
杰森:德威特先生,怎么了?你这么穿戴怎么像一根大香蕉啊?
Jason: Mr.Dewitt, what's wrong?And why are you dressed like some big Banana?
德威特先生:哦,刚才我在路上骑车兜风,突然想到该问问本,怎么又不申请参加高级再编班考试了.
Mr.Dewitt: Oh I was cycling in the neighborhood, and I thought I'd swing by
to check on why Ben didn't apply for the advanced placement exam
杰森:本!他讨厌考试.他连数数都不喜欢.
Jason: Ben!He hates tests.He'll even look for Waldo.
德威特先生:正如我所料.
Mr.Dewitt: Just as I thought.
德威特先生:他只会玩烟雾弹和追女孩.
Mr.Dewitt: This was obviously about smoke bombs and strippers.
杰森:正是这样.
Jason: Obviously.
迈克:爸爸,"大香蕉"呢
Mike: Dad, Where is the Banana.
杰森:他到那边去了.
Jason: He went that way.
迈克:谢天谢地,我要发大财了!
Mike: Thanks, just get ready for big bucks!
杰森:嘿,本-!
Jason: Hey Be-en!
本:哎!
Ben: Yah!
杰森:你的校长德威特先生来过了.
Jason: Our principal Mr.Dewitt was just here.
你参加什么高级再编班考试了吗?
Were you taking some advanced placement test?
本:是的,爸爸,
Ben: Yeah right, dad, but what would I do with that?
不过我该怎么办呢?你和我都知道我没有数学脑子.
We both know I'm no Einstein.
杰森:你是什么意思?
Jason: What do you mean by that?
本:哦,你是什么意思?我听见你对你的会计师说什么了."还是算了吧,本可没有数学脑子".
Ben: Well, what did you mean by it.I heard you when you told your accountant.Let's face it Ben is no Einstein.
杰森:很明显,我不是那个意思的,本?
Jason: Well obviously, I did not mean that way Ben?
本:是的,你是这么说的!
Ben: Yeah, well you said it!
本:你就是这个意思,因为你根本没想到我会听见.
Ben: And I know you meant it cuz you didn't even knew I was listening.
你觉得我是个笨蛋.你觉得我一辈子就是这样.我就是个笨蛋.
You think I am dumb and you've known me my whole life.I must be dumb!
杰森:不,本,不是.
Jason: No, Ben, No.
德威特先生:我是回来道歉的.刚才我没对你这么说,
Mr.Dewitt: I have a confession to make.
因为我不想让你觉得我是个笨蛋.
I did not tell you before because I did not wanna appear foolish in your eyes.
本放弃考试,那是我的错.他找我谈过,
It's my fault Ben's not taking that test.
我却嘲笑他,挖苦他.我还自得其乐.
He expressed interested and I scoffed, I belittled, I had a great time.
我打击他,只差叫他笨蛋了.
I did everything but call him stupid.
不过后来,我跟他的老师谈过.本现在的成绩都在优良以上.
Oh, since then I've talked to his teachers. Ben has a 3.0 average.
杰森:优良?
Jason: A 3.0?
德威特先生:我知道这是无稽之谈.是我害了你儿子.
Mr.Dewitt: I know.Pigs are flying. I have ruined your son.
家长们信任我才把孩子送来.
People trust me with their children and I, I break'em.
而我却让他们失望了.星期一早上我就递辞职报告.
Monday morning I am turning in my resignation.
杰森:德威特先生,这不是你的错,是我的.
Jason: Mr.Dewitt, it's not your fault it's mine!
德威特先生:哦,谢谢上帝,
Mr.Dewitt: Oh thank God.Oh to think I almost quit!
哦,我差点辞职了!我还是骑着我的车兜风去吧.
Guess I better get my Schwinn in motion.
迈克:笑一笑!
Mike: Smile!
德威特先生:噢,你这个臭小子…
Mr.Dewitt: That, that, that, doesn't..
德怀特:嗨,开萝尔?
Dwight: Hi Carol?
开萝尔:哈罗.
Carol: Hello.
德怀特:早上发生了一件很奇怪的事.一个穿蓝披肩的姑娘闯到我家,
Dwight: The strangest thing happened this morning.
把松饼扔了我姐姐一脸,
A woman in blue plaid came to my door, threw muffins at my sister,
骂了她,然后跑了.
threatened her and then ran.
开萝尔:你姐姐?
Carol: Your sister?
德怀特:是的,伊莱恩是个空姐.
Dwight: Yeah, Elaine's a stewardess,
每次飞到肯尼迪机场,她就来看我.我不明白的是为什么扔松饼.
she visits whenever she flies into Kennedy, and my question is why muffins.
开萝尔:噢.
Carol: Uhhm.
德怀特:你很美,像早上盛开的花朵.
Dwight: You positively blew with this hour of the morning.
开萝尔:真的?
Carol: I do?
德怀特:我想请你见见伊莱恩,
Dwight: I'd love for you to come meet Elaine,
能带些松饼来吗?虽然不太好吃,
wanna come over for some muffins?
但却是不花钱的.
They're not very good, but what the heck they're free.
(唱)马克赖斯:"野马萨利…你最好让野马慢下来…"
(SING) Mark Rice: "Mustang Sally... Guess you better slow mustang down..."
杰森:野马萨利,这是我最爱听的老歌.
Jason: Mustang Sally, it's one of my old-time favorites.
本,我不该说那些无聊的话,就像不了解你似的.
Ben I had no business say something like this, like a stranger.
本:没什么,你不是故意的.
Ben: Alright, you didn't mean it anyway.
杰森:不,我是故意的.以前,我真的以为你没有数学脑子.
Jason: No, I meant it.I really did think you were no Einstein.
谢谢你了,爸爸.
Ben: Thanks a lot Dad.
杰森:我也很笨.
Jason: Neither was I.
Ben (reads Jason's score card): D, C, F, C minus, D.Is this you
杰森:哦,是.
Jason: Uh-hum.
本:你真是没有数学脑子.你真是笨的够戗.
Ben: You really were no Einstein.You were barely a Trigger.
杰森:就是这样的.本,就连爱因斯坦小时候也没有数学脑子.你知道他上学时的故事吗?我们有些人将来才能发挥自己的潜能.
Jason: Boy it is Ben, even Einstein was no Einstein, you know he grew up
that at school?Some of us don't' show our potential until later
本:你是说,有一天我会发挥自己的潜能吗?
Ben: So you're saying that some day I'll start showing my potential?
杰森:你已经发挥了,本.
Jason: You already have Ben.
去年,你跟妈妈一起在家学习的时候就开始了.
Last year when you started studying at home with your mother.
本:哦,当她跟我一起学的时候,我就来劲.
Ben: Well, that's fine when she was working with me.
杰森:不是这样的.你妈妈只是帮你找回信心,
Jason: That's not true.Your mother gave you confidence she got you started.
让你开始.但那以后就是你自己在学习.
But then you went out you took over by yourself.
你凭自己的努力已经是优等生了.
You became a 3.0 student on your own.
本:我做到了,是不是?
Ben: I did, didn't I?
杰森:而我说了愚蠢的话,差点让你放弃努力.
Jason: And I almost blew the whole thing with that dumb remark.
本:但当时你为什么这么说呢?
Ben: But then why did you say that?
杰森:哦,你是在我们这个家长大的.我习惯地给你们都贴上了标签.
Jason: Oh you live in a family Ben, you tend to put labels on people.
开萝尔是一个聪明的孩子;迈克是个帅小伙;你,
You know Carol was the smart one, Mike was the charming one, and then you,
却总还干一些向狗窝吐痰这样的蠢事.
you're the one who goofy-glued sticky saliva into the dog-house.
杰森:不过这几个月来,你完全变了个样.
Jason: You got through this change these whole last few months Ben,
这一切就发生在我的眼前,而我却浑然不知.
well and it happened right under my nose,
我真对不起,我没注意到.我真希望能收回说过的话.
and I did not even see it I am so sorry. I missed it, please.
可我已经说了..你能原谅我吗?
I wish I could take back what I said, but I can't. Will you forgive me?
本:我想会的.
Ben: I guess.
杰森:就像你一样,我们重新开始,好吗?
Jason: Like you start over, clear the slate?
本:好的.
Ben: Sure.
杰森:太好了.
Jason: Right.
杰森:嘿,我说,
Jason: Hey, look, would you be interested in helping me input some data
你有兴趣帮我把这些数据输入到电脑里吗?
into the computer?
本:开玩笑吧.你相信我能做这样的事吗?
Ben: You're kidding.You trust me to do something like that?
杰森:当然,我信.
Jason: Sure I would.
本:爸爸,这太重要了,你这样对我.你付我钱吗?
Ben: Dad, this means so much, coming from you. Will you pay me?
杰森:我会付钱的.
Jason: I'll pay you.
本:哦,爸爸.
Ben: Oh, Dad, this means so much! Coming from you.
这太重要了!你这样对我.屏幕:1991年11月29日.
Screen: November 29th, 1991. Ben Seaver arrived to take the New York state
本西沃赶去参加纽约州高级编班考试.不幸的是,考试日期是在30号.
advanced placement exam, unfortunately the test was scheduled for the 30th.
小伙子第二天红着脸又返回到考场,并顺利地通过了考试.
Red-faced, the boy returned the next day and passed with flying colors.
同一天,教师休息室里有一枚烟雾弹爆炸.
That same day a smoke bomb was detonated in the faculty lounge.
至今没有捉到任何肇事者.00:22:21,700
To date, no suspects have been apprehended.